# OGAMBA PATRICK JUNIOR

Software Engineer, Mobile Developer, FullStack Developer

### Contact

#### Address:

Carrefour Nouvelle Route Cite Sic, Douala, Cameroon

#### Phone:

+ 237 670157564

#### **Email:**

ogambapatrickjunior@gmail.com

# Languages

- English
- French

## Education

### **Software Engineering**

- University Institute of the Golf of Guinee (IUG).

# Socials

### **MY PORTFOLIO**

- Click to Visit

#### **GITHUB**

PatrickJunior007

#### LINKEDIN

Patrick Junior

## Certifications

- Higher National Diploma (HND) in Software Engineering.
- Bachelor Degree in Software Engineering.

# Summary

Software Engineer with two years of experience, I successfully combined my studies with work and other commitments showing myself to be self-motivated, organized and capable of working in collaboration with others. In addition to that I'm very hardworking, learn quickly and easily.

# Skills Highlights

### Software Engineer 09/2021 till present

- Have skills in Graphic Designing.
- Experienced in modeling of applications.
- Well-versed in web development tools including HTML, CSS, JQuery, WordPress, Bootstrap.
- Experienced in Search Engine Optimization (SEO).
- Skilled in programming languages such as PHP, MySQL, and JavaScript.
- Skilled in React Native, React and Nuxt Js Framework.
- Clear and understanding knowledge in the versioning tools Git and GitHub.
- Skilled in the PHP backend framework Laravel for web application development.
- Have Skills in developing REST APIs using Node and Express.
- Other Skills: MongoDB, FireBase, TypeScript, Testing, Cucumber, Cypress.

# Experience

### Software Engineer (01/03/2022 – Present)

#### NKAP SARL

- Worked on several web applications using technologies like Nuxt JS, React, PHP, Laravel and WordPress.
- Took part in testing and automating web applications and software using technologies like Cypress and Cucumber.
- Took part in the Development of Mobile applications using React Native, TypeScript, Expo RN, REST APIs and Firebase.
- Worked on the SEO of several clients' websites.

### **Frontend Developer** (19/09/2022 – 29/11/2022)

#### SIKATRONIC GROUP

Using technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.

### **Intern** (19/09/2021 – 19/01/2021)

#### 237SOFT

 Gain most of my experience working for the company and took part into projects connected with both Web app, App development and Modeling.